#### **Contact Info**



+91 8939266125



Chennai



sharathdfire@gmail.com



LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/sharath-chandran-dillibabu-50ab92153

#### **SKILLS**

#### **Manual Testing**

- Good knowledge with SDLC.
- Exposure in Black box testing.
- Good knowledge in STLC.
- ➤ Good knowledge in Defect life cycle.
- Good exposure in Test plan.
- Levels of Testing.
- Agile Methodology.

#### **Automation Testing**

- Core Java
- Selenium Web-driver.
- TestNG Framework.
- Cucumber BDD Framework.
- Git and Maven.
- Management tools- JIRA, RedMine.

#### **Internship & Certifications**

- Manual and Automation Training, Feb 2018 to May 2018.
- Design Intern in PECPL, Oct 2017 to Jan 2018.
- Pipeline Design Training, Feb 2017 to June 2017.

# SHARATH CHANDRAN D

# SOFTWARE TEST ENGINEER

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a Quality Analyst with holistic knowledge of software testing. I have 3+ years of experience in all levels of testing, including functional, integration, system, and user acceptance. Worked on multiple projects involving both web & mobile based applications.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

July 2021 – Present

# Indium Software (India) Private Ltd.

Software Testing Engineer

- Analyzing the Scope documents and Identifying the Test Scenarios.
- Building up the Test Cases and Involved in peer review of Test Cases.
- Executing the Test cases and tracking the defect in defect tracking tool.
- Preparing the Test summary reports.

# May 2018 - June 2021

#### SolvEdge Technology (India) Private Ltd.

Software Testing Engineer (Trainee)

- Analyzing the user requirements and Identifying the Test Scenarios.
- Building up the Test Cases and Involved in peer review of Test Cases.
- Executing various testing phases and tracking the defect in defect tracking tool.
- Locating the web elements in Selenium WebDriver using Xpath.
- Preparing and executing of the Java scripts using Selenium-TestNG framework.
- Code development and execution of the scripts using Selenium- Cucumber BDD framework.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### CHS Cigna PDP (Health care)

#### **Project Description**

Enrolling a member in a web based application which provides the members Medicare details (Prescription Drug Plan) for the CHS.

## **Testing Knowledge / Application Tested**

- > Automation and Manual testing.
- Web Based Applications.
- Mobile Applications.

# **Educational History**

- Bachelor of Engineering 72.4%
  (08/2012- 04/2016)
  Prince Dr. K. Vasudevan College of Engineering and Technology
- HSC- 75.5%
   (07/2011- 04/2012)

  Prince Matriculation Higher Sec.
  School, Chennai.
- SSLC-84.4%
   (07/2009-04/2010)

  Prince Matriculation Higher Sec.
  School, Chennai.

#### My Indium App / TRIMMS

## **Project Description**

A Web and Mobile based application designed for employee to maintain the timesheet. Also it provides the updated news of HR and Marketing Announcements for the employees.

# **Recovery Coach (Health care)**

#### **Project Description**

A Web and Mobile based application designed to guide the patients during their entire surgical journey. Also it prompts notification alerts to patients and physicians in case of emergency.

# **Hospital Reported Outcomes (HRO)**

# **Project Description**

A Web based application clearly explains about the hospital performance and helps in to improve the quality of the hospitals.

# **EchoLog (Mobile App)**

#### **Project Description**

EchoLog is made to improve on paper logbook and makes better way to log your ultrasound scan reports digitally.